

ABOUT ME

Software development is my passion. With a background in network management and experience in network administration, I am excited to transition into software development to create innovative solutions, applying my technical skills and love for programming.

- 0906 489 1148 / 0999 985 6634
- nicocbnora@gmail.com
- #12 Tamaray St, Atulayan Sur, Tuguegarao City

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Electronics and Communications Engineering

University of Saint Louis Tuguegarao 2011 - 2016

SKILLS

Software Development

- HTML
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Express.JS
- JavaScript MongoDB
- React.JS
- PostgreSQL
- Node.JS

Soft Skills

- Agile Philosophy
- Scrum Methodology
- o Time Management
- Teamwork
- Critical Thinking

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

PORTFOLIO

https://nicholainora.github.io/ udemy-html-css-portfolio/

NICHOLAI CHRISTOPHER NORA

Electronics Engineer

RELATED WORK EXPERIENCE

COMPUTER MAINTENANCE TECHNOLOGIST II

DEPARTMENT OF INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATIONS TECHNOLOGY

2023 - Present

- Troubleshooting of LAN/WAN Configurations, including IP routing and switching.
- Provide technical support by performing preventive maintenance, basic testing, and corrective maintenance on the office's Data Center peripherals, servers, and computer networks.
- Ensure the system, procedures, and standards are strictly implemented in its daily operation, including incidence, troubleshooting alerts, daily logs, and escalation.

ENGINEER I

DEPARTMENT OF INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATIONS TECHNOLOGY

- Monitored and provided reports of all operational beneficiary sites.
- Provided technical support by performing preventive maintenance, basic testing, and corrective maintenance on the Wi-Fi sites, Internet connectivity, and networks.
- Surveyed and inspected sites including creation of report.
- · Ensured completion and proper turnover of documents to the Project's
- Tracked work schedules and ensured timely issuance of documents.

NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR

DEPARTMENT OF INTERIOR AND LOCAL GOVERNMENT

2020-2021

- Performed administration of systems and servers related to WAN and LAN, VoIP security and network equipment for the purpose of ensuring availability of services of authorized users.
- · Designed and created computer networks and network engineering for the purpose of ensuring effective and efficient computer operations.
- Troubleshoot system network problems, diagnosing and solving hardware and software faults.
- Configured and installed client/server network software for upgrading and maintaining network and telecommunication system.

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

GOIT - PHILIPPINES FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP 2023 - 2024

UDEMY - WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

PINOY SEO - SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION BOOTCAMP 2024